<module>
	<rawname>ringgroups</rawname>
	<name>Ring Groups</name>
	<version>2.2.16.2</version>
	<type>setup</type>
	<category>Inbound Call Control</category>
	<description>
		Creates a group of extensions that all ring together. Extensions can be rung all at once, or in various 'hunt' configurations. Additionally, external numbers are supported, and there is a call confirmation option where the callee has to confirm if they actually want to take the call before the caller is transferred.
	</description>
	<changelog>
		*2.2.16.2* #2193 moh path hardcoded
		*2.2.16.1* bump for rc1
		*2.2.16* #1961 changed to allow leading 0 extensions
		*2.2.15.2* fixed bug install.php not converting destinations properly for new findmefollow format
		*2.2.15.1* #2057 don't strip CID prefix if no prefix is being added
		*2.2.15* #2024 provide alert when adding duplicate group number
		*2.2.14.3* bumping to remove checksum error
		*2.2.14.2* changed freePBX to FreePBX
		*2.2.14.1* merge findmefollow/core extension destinations if any
		*2.2.14* Fixed bug where nested CID prefixes ends up removing part of the valid CID info
		*2.2.13* introduction of firstavailable firstnotonphone strategy that only rings one extension and optionally skips callwaiting REQUIRE CORE r3652
		*2.2.12* never allow group to include itself as nnn# and create infinite loop
		*2.2.11* changed _ALERT_INFO to __ALERT_INFO ('_' -> '__') so it is infinitely inheritted into the dialplan
		*2.2.10* Added BLKVM DB tree to fix inability to transfer a received call to another user, and make NODEST stuff work overall
		*2.2.9* Modified NODEST stuff to improve some cases where it was still failing, and improve '#' transfer scenarios
		*2.2.8* Allow ringall-prim as well as ringall for strategies with confirmation (#1408)
		*2.2.7* Add tool tip for Group Description (#1459)
		*2.2.6* Add NODEST so that destination (often vm) is not taken if called from queue or ringgroup and such is honored for childeren
		*2.2.5* Modified flyover help - since moh works with confirmation now
		*2.2.4* Added sound files for default confirmation messages
		*2.2.3* Clarification on help message if you want to ring follow-me and other non-extension numbers
		*2.2.2* Forgot to add default starting RG number as 600
		*2.2.1* Cleanup of the UI, remove workaround of formatting bugs with previous UI
		*2.2* First release for FreePBX 2.2 - Fixed compatibility issue with new UI</changelog>
	<menuitems>
		<ringgroups>Ring Groups</ringgroups>
	</menuitems>
	<location>release/2.3/ringgroups-2.2.16.2.tgz</location>
	<md5sum>8b6f4ede864e9c706df56025682d3582</md5sum>
</module>
